hello there it's the Marvel and today is
tutorial video in this
video manual life policy through gcash
account so all you need to do is to log
into your gcash account once log in just
go to bills the one on the upper right
hand of the screen once you're on the
bills you can definitely search manual
life right
away man life China Bank manual Life
Financial plans and manual life
Philippines you're going to have to ask
your financial advisor to make sure
which one but for me it's Financial or
manual live Philippines so you're going
to have to put how much is the desired
amount or how much you're going to pay
for me it's
10,210 because I'm actually quarterly
and then the account number account
number is going to be your policy number
so you're going to have to make sure
with that that's available on your um
manual life app and then lastly um you
have to put your email address which is
actually optional but it's a good thing
to get your references as well and then
that's it you have to click done and
then confirm on the upper right hand of
the screen and you're good to go now for
future references though um you can
definitely save this into your favorites
just to make
sure information moving forward so
that's it thank you again for watching
and if you're new to this Channel please
don't forget to subscribe again this is
Al the Marvel thank you so much for
watching have a great day bye